All right, recruits.
Welcome to service school.
This is Lene, your hospitality hostess.
Hello.
I look forward to working with you.
Now you hold on just a moment, Commoner.
Who gave you permission to
exploit my servant in this matter?
Guilty.
I asked her to find us
a qualified instructor.
You did what?
Nobles like us don't know the
first thing about service.
That's gotta change if
we hope to run a cafe.
Can you imagine the horror?
We can't go into the Foundation Day Fair
without any hosting skills to speak of.
But, thankfully, the problem's solved.
You don't mind, do you?
Now then, as I'm sure you're
all aware, I am a commoner.
And I'm a servant as well.
I'm sure some of you may find the
idea of being taught by me appalling.
However, focusing on status will distract
you from serving your customers properly.
And that's why, until their
preparations are complete...
You all will address me as instructor!
Lene!
What in the world has gotten into you?
Ridiculous!
You really expect us to
take orders from a commoner?
Take instructions from an expert.
How can you say that, Prince Yu?
And then there's this guy.
He may be a servant to the royal
family, but he's still a noble,
upturned nose and all.
I suppose it's decided then.
We're all counting on your tutelage, Lene.
I'm sorry, Miss Claire.
I believe you meant Instructor Lene.
Service is about giving everything to your
master and expecting nothing in return.
It's an art crafted from
the sincerest compassion.
Read this and enter me when I speak.
Yes, Instructor Lene!
What is the essence of a maid's work?
Service and devotion, Instructor Lene!
The first skill a maid must learn.
A polite greeting, Instructor Lene!
Let's hear it all together,
loudly and clearly!
Good afternoon, Master, and welcome home!
I can't hear you!
Don't you look at me in the eye!
Good afternoon, Master, and welcome home!
I hope you two don't think
you're exempt from all this!
Now, what's more with feeling?
Good afternoon, Master, and welcome home!
Well, that was quite
the ordeal, wasn't it?
I never knew you had such a
fearsome alter ego, Linnaeus.
I apologize, Miss Clare.
Perhaps I did get a bit overzealous.
Even so, I suppose it
shouldn't come as a surprise.
You always have been quite different from
the other maids since the day we met.
This is your new maid, Miss Clare.
She will be serving you personally.
Go on, introduce yourself.
My name is Lene Oriseu.
It's my pleasure to serve you.
You think that I care what your name is?
I don't!
Why should I when you'll be
quitting within a week anyway?
She was a handful from
the very beginning, huh?
Since her parents were either
busy or traveling all the time,
Miss Claire wasn't raised with firm
values or consistent nurturing.
She became selfish and hard to manage.
Commoner!
My name is Lene, Miss Claire.
I already told you I don't care!
Now stop prattling and become a horse!
A horse, miss?
I know you lack education, but
do not even know what a horse is?
I know what a horse is, but
why do you want me to be one?
Because I'm in the mood
to go riding, obviously.
So, get down on your hands and knees now!
Miss Claire, please don't
ask me to be a horse.
What did you say?
You're supposed to say
yes as you command! No.
Why, you little - Because nobles
shouldn't sully themselves that way.
I can't allow someone like you to
sit on the back of a lowly, commoner.
I'll admit I'm impressed by
how well you know your place.
You might even have long-term
potential here, commoner.
Very well then.
I will allow you to serve as
my maid for the time being.
Make sure not to disappoint me.
I appreciate it, miss.
Aw, even when you were
little you were gullible.
Uh, I mean, you are adorable.
Oh no, I heard you insult me.
Don't you try to gloss over it.
And it's funny to think that Lene
has always been this stubborn.
I mean that she's been so reliable.
You're gonna be a huge help to
us at the fair, Miss Instructor.
Thank you.
You too, Miss Claire.
Hmm, that goes without saying.
If I'm going to bother to learn a
new skill, I demand to be the best.
All right, let's get to servicing.
We'll service the crap out of them.
Yeah!
Do you want me no hold on?
Yes, I know!
No, I don't want you
to know what you want.
Do you want me no hold on?
Yes, I know!
No, I want only you!
Oh
Well, you look rather decent,
though I suppose servant's
clothing would suit a commoner.
Oh, my stars, Miss Claire just
gave me a real compliment.
I was insulting you, you rube!
Well, Misha, what do you think?
Wow, it suits you perfectly, Prince Yu.
You look quite handsome as well.
Thank you.
That's very kind.
The shift schedule's posted here.
We rotate between prepping and serving.
We'll have to take turns for breaks.
Do you suppose we'll start
any time soon? Let's go!
I'm so ready for this!
Good afternoon, master, and welcome home!
Right this way.
Here you are.
Have you decided what you'd
like to order, master?
Of course, master.
I'll bring it right out.
Gentlemen, our finest plight of
roast beef sandwiches for you.
Has everything been to
your liking, master?
I do hope so.
Pardon, miss Claire, a
customer has requested you.
Don't keep your customer
waiting, miss Claire.
Yes!
Instructor Lene, ma 'am!
I appreciate your patience.
Have you had sufficient time to decide?
Ah! He-he-he!
Look at you bottling the rage
in the name of professionalism!
What a gentleman!
Commoner, if you do not desist, I
will not hesitate to slap you! Really?
Do you promise?
Oh, never mind.
I nearly forgot I'm dealing
with a complete degenerate.
What would you like to order?
Let me see.
How about the sandwich and
creme brulee special, please?
And may I get you something
to drink with that as well?
Your tears on the rocks, please.
Do not test me, you little twit!
What would you like to drink, Master?
May I recommend the hurry
and get out of my sight?
It's quite refreshing!
Maybe just black tea after the meal.
It will be my pleasure.
Oh, and I'd love a sight of
that Miss Claire sweet stuff.
I'm afraid we're all out of that.
And that'll be all for today, right?
You did a great job.
And now I shall pledge
your head as reward.
Pardon me.
Excuse me, miss.
Yes, what is it, sir?
Hi, can I add something
to my order, please?
You shall have your
vengeance one day, Claire.
Patience.
It's going so well.
Thank you for your patience.
Please come in, master.
Prince Yu, do you have a minute?
I really need to talk to you.
Please, I won't take...
We do not allow cutting in this line.
Matt!
We'll talk soon.
I promise.
I didn't expect it to be this busy Hello?
Some help, please? Coming!
Apologies for the work.
That took you long enough!
How dare you make His
Highness wait for service?
Do you have any idea who this man is?
Only the illustrious Crown
Prince of the Empire of Loro.
Behold, His Imperial
Highness, Marcel Loro!
You will take his order immediately.
Of course, sir.
I almost forgot about this guy.
If he stays true to the
game, this is gonna suck.
Bring me your finest
dish made with dodo bird.
His highness loves the dodo.
I knew it.
I hate to disappoint,
but I'm afraid we don't have
anything with dodo bird on our menu.
No, what's this?
If his highness wants dodo,
then you will bring it to him.
Believe me, sir, I wish I could,
but it's a very rare delicacy.
You're not likely to find Dodo served
anywhere in the entire of our kingdom.
This is the worst.
Prince Marcel shows up at
the Foundation Day Fair just
to be rude and make impossible
demands of the heroine.
He's only there as a
challenge in the game.
When played as intended, one of the
romanceable characters, a .k .a.
the princes, comes to her rescue.
And this is the part where I temporarily
regret not raising their affection levels.
It's so, so much worse, IRL.
Do you expect me to go out into the
wilderness and tackle a dodo for you to cook?
Because if that's the case,
if I have to wrestle a dodo...
Please forgive my
interruption, Prince Marcel.
Miss Claire?
Ah, there is one among
you fluent in lower knees.
What is your name, young lady?
Claire Francois, Your Highness.
Might I make a suggestion?
We do serve an exotic dish
made with a very rare sauce.
For exclusive guests, that is.
This item is so rare.
Only a select few have ever
tasted it here in Bower.
I'm certain your highness will enjoy it.
Very well, I'll trust your recommendation.
I am delighted to hear you say so.
Come, let's go.
Can you believe the
nerve of that narcissist?
This is why I can't stand
these new money monarchies.
Did you make note?
Pompous fools like him will
always cave if you butter them up.
That is valuable advice.
Roger that.
Thank you so much.
Not only for the advice,
but for helping me.
Well, I certainly didn't do it for
you, if that's what you're implying.
Just go serve him his egg
sandwich and leave me to my rest.
Mayonnaise hasn't reached Loro yet,
so remind him that it's a delicacy.
On it!
What?
Oh, nothing.
I was just remembering
something, that's all.
Miss Claire, please.
I promise I'm fine
wearing the maid uniform.
Don't be ridiculous, Lene.
It's absolutely unacceptable for anyone
who serves me not to own a single gown.
Simply lovely.
May we try this one on, please?
But of course, Miss Claire.
What is this?
Who allowed this commoner in here?
This is no place for your
kind to linger, girl.
Get out at once.
Pardon me a moment, but has my
servant done something imprudent?
Ah, fluent in Loranese at your age.
You must be receiving a fine education.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I am the daughter of Dolph Red
Swat and Minister of Finance.
My name is Claire.
Hmm? Hmm? What?
King LaSalle is introducing a policy
for the betterment of commoners?
He is indeed, your highness.
I brought her here to help the king
measure how far we still have left to go.
How odd.
But as a visiting dignitary, I suppose I
must adhere to the King of Bowers' wishes.
I shall overlook this incident.
I am delighted to hear you say so.
Miss Claire.
I'm sorry you had to go through that.
And all because of me.
They're so frustrating!
Stupid, irritating royals! Miss Clare?
The monarchy of Loro is absolutely horrid!
How dare that prince mistreat
a member of my house!
Listen to me, Lene.
You are my servant.
Do you understand?
That makes you the highest-ranked
commoner in this entire kingdom!
Don't let anyone treat you like that!
Yes, as you command.
Very good!
tipo
Ray, take your break, my time has come.
Okay, good luck out there big guy.
Oh, hello, Miss Claire.
Are you taking your break now, too?
You did such a great
job handling customers.
I'm truly impressed.
I don't know why that's so surprising.
I'm the Minister of Finance's daughter.
Putting on a front for people
is second nature to me.
Well, for what it's worth, I prefer
it when you're your usual honest self.
There's nothing honest about me.
I already told you before, didn't I?
I'm well aware of what
kind of personality I have.
Please stop.
It makes me sad to hear you talk
about yourself so negatively.
Excuse me?
I do not need your pity, you...
What do you think you're doing?
Inviting you out.
There's a whole fair out there
just waiting to be explored.
Please, Ms.
Claire, it'd be an honor to escort you.
There's so much to do!
Where would you like to go first?
No food or drinks, thank you very much.
Not from here.
I refuse to pollute my body with junk.
Your loss!
Let's try this!
Is this one of your vile jokes?
Oh, I'm sorry, Miss Claire.
I almost forgot you're afraid of ghosts.
I'm not afraid, you fool.
I was simply taken aback by your
interest in something so juvenile.
Oh, good.
Then you'll be just fine.
Two students for the hell house, please?
Come in, Art! Let me go!
You okay back there?
I'm fine.
It's just a haunted house.
Well, if you need a little
snuggle, I'm here for you.
What?
Of all the ridiculous suggestions...
Yeah!
I'm so exhausted.
You do seem to be wilting a bit.
How about I go get you something to drink?
Yes, thank you.
But nothing silly or extravagant.
Water will do just fine. A tea!
Sign up to join a good cause!
Excuse me?
You're Ray Taylor, aren't you?
The star commoner who got into the
Royal Academy at the top of her class?
Um, I guess so, yeah. My name is Matt.
I'm a commoner here on
scholarship, just like you!
So, want to join the commoner movement?
We're currently trying to recruit
more supporters to our cause.
Here, this is our flyer.
Excuse me.
Who are you, and why are you filling my
servant's head with radical nonsense?
Wait, are you...
Claire Francois?
A movement seeking equality
between nobles and commoners?
You're a fool for committing
this backwash to paper.
Let's go.
The audacity.
I wondered what was keeping you.
You shouldn't waste your
time on those idiots.
The thing is, I don't think
their beliefs are idiotic at all.
I see.
You agree with them?
Maybe.
But it wouldn't matter to me if
I were a commoner or a noble.
I'd still prefer to serve you.
Oh yeah, I almost forgot. Here.
I wanted to give you this.
It's an amulet. Yes.
A charm to help you
find the love you seek.
I hope things work out
between you and Prince Thane.
You're as confusing as
you are frustrating.
As much as you might like
to tease and joke around,
I think you really mean it when you
say that you're in love with me.
Well, yeah, of course I do.
Yet you give me this, and support me
getting together with Prince Thane.
That doesn't make any sense.
Doesn't it, though?
Your happiness means the world to me.
I want that more than having
my love for you returned.
I still don't understand.
Of all the people out there, why
in the world would you choose me?
Because you're the one who
brought my heart back to life.
I worked myself to exhaustion every day.
My life was all about the next deadline.
I could barely breathe from the pressure.
And there was no way to escape!
But amid all that?
It's hard to explain.
And chances are, you wouldn't
believe me if I tried.
But you rescued me.
Honestly, I have all the
absurd things for you to say.
Oh, never mind.
Clearly, you don't mean
to give me a real answer.
We ought to head back anyway.
Really?
Isn't that late already?
In that case, Ms.
Claire, please give me your...
I'm through playing pretend with you.
Huh?
You and I are a noble and a commoner.
Nothing more, and nothing less.
Do you understand?
Do you really mean that? Let's go.
I don't want to return too late.
Thank you.
How do you think I'm going to do this?
I'm not sure how it's a real feeling,
but it's not just the feeling that I'm
thinking I'm thinking about how you do it,
it's a real thing.
I'm thinking that I'm gonna be a person.
When I'm thinking about your
heart, it's a big thing.
I don't even know what you've ever done.
I don't know what you've done.
Ten sheets of parchment, two bottles
of ink, and one ball of leather thread.
Seems like we got all we need
why do we have to do the shopping
well it's part of our job Despite
the name knights mostly run errands
and do office work fair day is
an exception There are so many
memories i'll treasure from fair
day like my date with miss claire
My looks like there's quite
the commotion out here
loretta peppy Can you
tell me what's happening?
Of course, Miss Claire.
It's awful.
Apparently, there was a fight between
one of the commoners and a noble.
Prince Hugh's attendant mastered deed.
He attacked a student in
the commoner movement.
Miss Claire!
We've got a case.
Consider it solved!
I swear, by the name of Claire Francois!
Wait, no, I don't.
The only thing keeping me going
is the ability to tease you.
Loath as I am to admit it, I believe that.